MUHAMMAD HAMZA KABEER

MERN STACK DEVELOPER

Location: Karachi, Pakistan | Location: Karachi, Pakistan | Portfolio: mdhamzakabeer.github.io/myportfolio
Contact: 03401952337 | Github | https://github.com/mdhamzakabeer
Linkedin: | https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammad-hamza-kabeer

SUMMARY

MERN stack developer with 1+ years of experience in web development, penetration testing, and e-commerce. Skilled in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React, Node.js, and security testing. Currently enhancing expertise through ongoing MERN stack and mobile app development courses

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5 Tailwind css Git ,Firebase, figma, vercel

CSS3 Bootstrap Responsive Design

Javascript React Typescript
Complete full stack solution Ux design Vite/React

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Penetration Tester Jan 2023 - Present

• - Performed penetration testing to identify and resolve security vulnerabilities over 1 year.

Daraz Store Owner 2021 - 2022

- Managed e-commerce store on Daraz, optimizing product listings and customer support.

MERN Stack Developer (Trainee)

Feb 2021 - Dec 2022

• Developing projects using React, Node.js, and MongoDB via Saylani MERN Stack Course. - Enhancing skills in responsive design and mobile app development through ongoing course.

EDUCATION

Undergraduate (Ongoing)

Virtual University, Pakistan

- Pursuing degree in SoftwareEngineering.

Diploma in Software Engineering

2020 - 2023

- Completed 3-year program at [JINNAH POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE], Karachi

Intermediate (Pre-Engineering)

2018 - 2020

- Board of Intermediate Education Karachi

Matriculation (Science)

2018

- Board of Secondary Education Karachi.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Languages: English / Urdu Native
- Certifications: MERN Stack Development, Saylani Mass IT Training, Oct 2024 Present
- Certifications: Associate Engineer (Diploma in Software Engineering, 3 Years), [JINNAH POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE], Karachi, 2021 - 2023
- Modern Web and Mobile Application Development, Oct 2024 Present